<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="AFSK">
    <Package name="Briefing">
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_DisplayName">
            <English>SerialKillers - Briefing</English>
            <Polish>SerialKillers - Odprawa</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_RulesEnabled">
            <English>Enable rules</English>
            <Polish>Włącz zasady</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_RulesEnabled_Description">
            <English>If enabled, suggested rules will be visible on the map in "SerialKillers" briefing section.</English>
            <Polish>Jeżeli włączone, proponowane zasady będą widoczne na odprawnie na mapie w zakładce "SerialKillers".</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules">
            <English>Rules</English>
            <Polish>Zasady</Polish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_1">
            <English>Cops are not allowed to use terrorist stashes/weapons. They may only use radios that find after neutralizing a terrorist.</English>
            <!-- <Polish>Policjanci nie mogą używać broni terrorystów ani skrytek z bronią. Mogą używać jedynie radia, które znajdą przy zneutralizowanym terroryście.</Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_2">
            <English>Cops are not allowed to kill, hurt or harm civilians in any other way without certainty that this is a terrorist. They may not use civilian vehicles either.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_3">
            <English>Cops are not allowed to sit in jail nor obstruct it in any way. They may only check if a prisoner is there, without moving him, they must leave immediately afterwards.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_4">
            <English>Only 1 police helicopter is allowed, with the same dedicated crew.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_5">
            <English>Terrorists should not use any cops-dedicated functionalities within police stations.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_6">
            <English>Terrorists are responsible for everyone's fun. Make it so the police doesn't die of boredom.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_7">
            <English>Driving off-road is allowed only when having off-road vehicle. Despite that, do not hide in forests/remote areas on purpose, as it's not fun.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_AFSK_Briefing_Rules_8">
            <English>Using vehicles as kamikaze kinetic projectiles is strictly forbidden due to how arma works, and it's not fun anyway.</English>
            <!-- <Polish></Polish> -->
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
